<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Survival Guide</string>

    <string name="about_flood">Water, one of the most common subslances known to man has become, through the years, a precious commodity. Water is required
    in practically all facets of human activities. And the need ofr water is enormous. It is roughly proportional to the population!\n\n
    However, the Philippines is blessed with a large number of rivers, lakes and stream. Thus, the lack of water has never been a real problem.
    Where an apparent scarcity exists, the difficulty is traceable to the uneven distribution of rainfall necessary to replenish water in revers,
    lakes and other bodies of water.\n\n
    From the foregoing technical definition, flood simply denotes a progressive abnormal increase in the elevation of the surface level of streamflow until it
    reaches a maximum height from which the level slowly drops to what is its normal level. The sequence described all takes place within a certain period of time.</string>

    <string name="about_fire">
        Fire is one of the most common disasters that could impact you and your family. As more people live closer and closer together, particularly as a result of urbanization, risks associated with fire increase.\n\n

House fires are predominantly accidental,
usually in relation to the use of indoor lamps, stoves or heaters that use an open flame.
While localized in effect, house fires ultimately affect hundreds of thousands of homes
a year world-wide. Fire spreads quickly and can easily engulf a home and neighboring structures within minutes.
    </string>

    <string name="flood_photo_credit">
        Floods brought by Tropical Cyclone (Ling Ling) Agaton, Philippines. \nPhoto: @ DDNewsLive
    </string>

    <string name="fire_photo_credit">
        Erik de Castro/Reuters
    </string>

    <string name="about_earthquake">
        ● Earthquakes have the capacity to cause
calamitous loss of property and life. These
sudden shifts in the earths crust happen swiftly
and without warning. A high magnitude
earthquake can alter a citys landscape in
seconds, rendering it unrecognizable.\n\n

● Despite this natural disasters unpredictability,
communities in earthquake-prone zones can take
measures to prepare for them. Earthquake
readiness increases your familys self-sufficiency
following an emergency. Experts agree - the less
you rely on emergency responders, the better
your chances of survival.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="earthquake_photo_credit">
        Rescuers call on persons trapped inside a shopping center that collpased in Padada, Davao del Sur during the 6.9 magnitude quake at 2:11 p.m. on Sunday, 15 December 2019. Photo by SAMANTHA BURGOS of Mindanao Times
    </string>

</resources>